# 前兩天粉絲送了一點這個狗糧給我們哦
A fan gave us some of these, dog food, a couple of days ago.
# 來餵一下小狗 他說我們的小狗太多啦
It's for the puppies. He said that we have too many puppies,
# 怕我們餵不起
and wondered whether we can still afford their food.
# 你看 這個粉絲太有愛心啦
Look! This fan is just too kind.
# 來 這個是
C'mon! This is...
# 哎呀 好香哦
Ayo! It smells great!
# 哎喲 這小狗很喜歡吃的
Ayo! The puppies like it so much.
# 來來來 有有有 別搶別搶別搶
Come, come, come! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Calm down, calm down, calm down!
# 額 通通都有 通通都有
Eh! Everybody has a share. Everybody has a share.
# 那麼激動幹嘛
Why are you so excited?
# 這小狗吃甚麼
What are the puppies eating?
# 這小狗吃的狗糧啊
The puppies are eating dog food.
# 來 給小狗吃
C'mon! Give it to the puppies.
# 這個是甚麼 肉餅
What is it? Meatloaf
# 狗
Puppies!
# 嗯 還有
Um! Here's more!
# 還要不要
Do you still want it?
# 嗯 不要
No, I don't.
# 啊
Ah!
# 哇 小狗你吃的[SIC]好快喲
Wa! Puppies, you eat really fast.
# 啊
Ah!
# 我從哪裡過來
How can I come to you?
# 啊
Ah?
# 去去去 這些不要
Chu chu chu~~! Don't take these!
# 把這個蓋子給你開了啊 快來給它餵呀
I'm opening the lid for you. Come and feed them!
# 嗯 我 我不餵小狗了哦
Um! I, I'm not feeding the puppies anymore.
# 怕甚麼
What are you afraid of?
# 你看 這是
Look! There are
# 那麼多餅幹
so many biscuits
# 這個不能吃的啊
Don't eat it.
# 誒
Eh?
# 大狗也吃這個餅幹啊
The big dogs are also eating the biscuits.
# 等下還是
I still need to...
# 怎麼只有6條小狗啦 還有一條
Why are here only six puppies? There's still a,
# 黑
black...
# 還有一條狗呢
Where's the remaining dog?
# 來 快點吃
Come! Come and eat!
# 好吃的
It's tasty.
# 你看 它們都吃飽了哦
Look! They've had enough,
# 都不怎麼想吃啦
and don't want anymore.
# 吃了好多啦
They've already eaten a lot.
# 要是我們買狗糧餵狗的話
If we were buying dog food to feed them,
# 虧大啦
it would be disaster.
# 太貴了這個
It's too expansive.
# 還是吃剩飯剩菜好哦
Table scarps is always the best option.
# 小黑
Blacky!
# 全廠就你最怕 你看 這個 牛奶味的 (註︰完全不懂這句的意思)
You are the most scared of, look, this is milk flavour.
# 好不好吃
Does it taste good?
# 要不要給一個草莓味的給你
Do I need to give you a strawberry flavour?
# 小黑 來
Blacky! Come here!
# 這個是草莓味的
This is strawberry flavour.
# 這個
This is...
# 黃色的
yellow.
# 我也不知道甚麼味的
I've no idea what flavour it is.
# 水果味的
Some fruits flavour
# 綠色的
It's green.
# 蔬菜味的
Veggie flavour
# 來 小黃(註︰多一個新名字了)
Come! Brownie.
# 就全部吃完啦
You've finished all?
# 不給它們吃啦
Alright, no more.
# 吃太多啦
They eat too much.
# 額 一下子全部吃完啦
Eh! They would finish it right away.
# 好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
# 感謝那位網友
Many thanks to that friend.